The tokenizer class you load from this checkpoint is not the same type as the class this function is called from. It may result in unexpected tokenization. 
The tokenizer class you load from this checkpoint is 'MBart50Tokenizer'. 
The class this function is called from is 'MBartTokenizer'.
Special tokens have been added in the vocabulary, make sure the associated word embeddings are fine-tuned or trained.
current considered lang:  en
file-path:  ./data/ner/panx/test-en_full.tsv
test on 10 samples: 

lanbel description: 
lang_label2ans:  {'O': 'XX is not an entity name.', 'LOC': 'XX is a location name.', 'PER': 'XX is a person name.', 'ORG': 'XX is an organization name.'}

idx2label: 
{0: 'O', 1: 'LOC', 2: 'PER', 3: 'ORG'}

lang_nclass:  4

{'sentence': 'Mayflower , Arkansas', 'span': 'Mayflower , Arkansas', 'sent_span_idx': (0, 0, 3), 'true_tag': 'LOC', 'consi_tag': 'O', 'target': 'Mayflower , Arkansas is not an entity name.'}
{'sentence': 'Mayflower , Arkansas', 'span': 'Mayflower , Arkansas', 'sent_span_idx': (0, 0, 3), 'true_tag': 'LOC', 'consi_tag': 'LOC', 'target': 'Mayflower , Arkansas is a location name.'}
{'sentence': 'Mayflower , Arkansas', 'span': 'Mayflower , Arkansas', 'sent_span_idx': (0, 0, 3), 'true_tag': 'LOC', 'consi_tag': 'PER', 'target': 'Mayflower , Arkansas is a person name.'}
{'sentence': 'Mayflower , Arkansas', 'span': 'Mayflower , Arkansas', 'sent_span_idx': (0, 0, 3), 'true_tag': 'LOC', 'consi_tag': 'ORG', 'target': 'Mayflower , Arkansas is an organization name.'}
{'sentence': 'Mayflower , Arkansas', 'span': 'Mayflower', 'sent_span_idx': (0, 0, 1), 'true_tag': 'O', 'consi_tag': 'O', 'target': 'Mayflower is not an entity name.'}
{'sentence': 'Mayflower , Arkansas', 'span': 'Mayflower', 'sent_span_idx': (0, 0, 1), 'true_tag': 'O', 'consi_tag': 'LOC', 'target': 'Mayflower is a location name.'}
{'sentence': 'Mayflower , Arkansas', 'span': 'Mayflower', 'sent_span_idx': (0, 0, 1), 'true_tag': 'O', 'consi_tag': 'PER', 'target': 'Mayflower is a person name.'}


args value: 
batch_size=20
column_no=1
data_name='panx'
data_path='data/ner/conll2003txt/test.txt'
delimiter='\t'
dir='./data/ner/panx/'
dtype='test'
eval_model='facebook/mbart-large-50'
eval_model_class='mbart'
eval_tokenizer='facebook/mbart-large-50'
fn_write_dir='results/ner/'
language='en'
max_span_width=6
model_name='panx_en_facebook\\mbart-large-50_mspan6_scoreTNSAT_generate_smallTrue'
n_class=4
path_temp='./data/ner/multilingual_NER_template.xlsx'
ratio_neg=1.5
score_fun='TNSAT'
temp_form='generate'
use_small_data=True
batch_size:  20
n_class:  4
idx2label:  {0: 'O', 1: 'LOC', 2: 'PER', 3: 'ORG'}
random_int:  32605698
f1, p, r, correct_preds, total_preds, total_correct:
0.07017543859649122 0.041237113402061855 0.23529411764705882 4.0 97.0 17.0
f1, p, r, correct_preds, total_preds, total_correct: 
0.07017543859649122 0.041237113402061855 0.23529411764705882 4.0 97.0 17.0
